I cannot believe that you didn't
tell me we are still married!
어떻게 우리가 아직 부부란
사실을 숨길 수가 있어
Look, I was going to tell you.
얘기하려고 했어
When? After the birth
of our first secret child?
언제? 몰래 애까지 낳고?
Ross didn't get the annulment.
We are still married!
혼인취소가 안 됐어
우린 아직 부부라고
- 뭐야?
- 어쩜 세상에!
-You're kidding.
-Oh, my God!
오빠
물론 잘한 짓은 아니지만
또 결혼에 실패할 순 없었어
It wasn't my best decision, but I
couldn't face another failed marriage.
At what point did you think
this was a successful marriage?
하나 물어보자, 어떤 면에서
이 결혼이 성공적인데?
Rach, come on. If you think about it,
it's actually kind of funny.
레이첼, 어떻게
생각하면 재미있잖아
Maybe it's best not to think about it.
그 생각은 안 하는 게 좋겠다
도저히 용서가 안 돼
내 심장이 다 벌렁거린다
This is inexcusable.
I'm shocked to my very core.
Phoebe, I told her you already knew.
피비, 너도 알고 있다는
얘기했어
Another lie. You have a sickness!
또 거짓말
아주 상습적이네
For my own peace of mind,
are you married to any more of us?
노파심에서 묻는데 우리 중
누구랑 또 결혼한 건 아니지?
Look, Rach, I was going to tell you.
레이첼, 얘기하려고 했어
내 방식대로 하고 싶었거든
I just wanted to do it in my own way.
Yes, silently, with no words.
그래, 무언의 대화로
야, 야, 야, 야, 야!
야...
Look, in Ross' defense, okay....
로스 입장에서 말해볼게
괜찮지?
The One With Joey's Porsche
Someone left their keys.
누가 키를 두고 갔네?
To a Porsche.
우, 포르쉐다
-Are these yours?
-Yeah. That's what I drive.
건터 차예요?
그래, 내가 모는 거야
시간 당 4달러 벌어서
350년 동안 저축했지
I make 4 bucks an hour.
I saved up for 350 years.
Did anybody lose their keys?
키 잃어버린 분?
그냥 분실물 함에 넣어둬
Put them in the lost and found.
There's a lost and found?
분실물 함이 있어?
My shoe!
내 신발이잖아
You left a shoe here?
신발을 두고 갔냐?
I didn't realize till I got home.
I wasn't gonna walk back with one shoe.
집에 가서야 알았는데
한 짝만 신고 내려올 순 없잖아
I'll go find that guy's car
and leave a note on the windshield.
아무래도 이 사람 차를 찾아서
메모를 남겨두는 게 좋겠다
키를 찾으러 오면
네 신발 전해줄게
When he comes back for his keys,
I'll give him your shoe.
Great. Thanks.
고맙다
Oh, good. You guys are here.
Listen.
잘됐다, 여기들 있었구나
들어봐
How would you like to spend tomorrow
taking care of three cute puppies?
내일 진짜 귀여운 강아지
세 마리 돌보고 싶지 않니?
어머, 그거 정말 재미있겠다
My God! What a fun day!
Sounds great!
Yeah, all right.
좋지 뭐
I'll bring them by tomorrow morning.
그럼 내일 아침에 데려올게
근데 사실은 강아지가 아니라
우리 동생네 세쌍둥이야
By the way, they're not
actually puppies.
They're Frank and Alice's triplets.
See you.
그럼 또 보자
워! 워! 워! 뭐?
What?
Please, please, please?
Frank and Alice...
제발, 제발, 제발, 제발, 제발
걔들이 세쌍둥이를 부탁했는데
asked me to baby-sit them.
I'm nervous. I've never done that.
난 경험이 없어서
겁난단 말이야
Don't worry. We'll do it.
걱정 마, 우리가 도와줄게
I'm gonna pass, because I was
kind of iffy when it was puppies.
난 빠질래, 강아지라고
할 때부터 안 내켰거든
왜 그래, 연습도 되고 좋잖아
Come on, Chandler. It'll give us
great practice for when...
people with babies come to visit.
손님이 아기 데려오면 써먹게
저 차가 아니잖아!
So I still have boxes here.
여기도 아직 내 짐이 있고
I still have boxes at Ross'.
로스 집에도 내 짐이 있는데
And I have nowhere to live.
내가 살 곳은 없어
I could so easily freak out right now.
왜 머리가 삥 돌지?
What about me? Denise is leaving town
for a while. I don't have a roommate.
난 어떻고
드니스가 여행가서
난 룸메이트도 없어
Well, maybe I could be
your roommate, Phoebe.
그럼 내가 룸메이트
하면 어떨까?
Maybe you could be my roommate!
네가 룸메이트 하면 되겠다
Well, there's an idea!
- 멋진 생각이다
- 그렇지?
정말 잘됐다
That would be great!
잠깐, 드니스는 언제 온대?
-How long is Denise gone for?
-She said she'd be back December 26th.
12월 26일에 올 거랬어
12월 26일이라
December 26th.
산타클로스인가 보네
Maybe she's Santa Claus.
Oh, look who it is.
My husband, the apple of my eye.
이게 누구야, 사랑하는
낭군님께서 오셨구만
Okay, I got us a court date
for tomorrow at 2...
좋아, 내일 2시까지
법원에 가야 돼
and I picked up all the forms.
서류도 다 챙겨왔어
I'll take care of it.
내가 처리할게
물론 네가 처리하겠다면
의심의 여지가 없겠지
Sure, if you say you'll take care
of it, I have no reason to doubt you.
Give me those forms.
이리 내놔
I'm gonna do this my way and I
don't wanna hear a peep out of you.
이제 내 방식대로 할 거야
꽁알거리지 마
- 그건 좋은데...
- 어? 꽁알거리네
-Okay, Rach, but..
-You're peeping!
Ross, I just got..
로스, 난 정말...
-Why did you do this?
-I told you..
대체 왜 그런 거야?
얘기했잖아...
I don't wanna hear
"three failed marriages."
그 세 번의 결혼 실패
얘긴 꺼내지도 마
너도 두 번 실패했으면
이해할 거야
If you'd had two failed marriages,
you'd understand.
그래? 네 덕분에
한 번은 실패했구나
Thanks to you, I'm halfway there.
Oh, I am so mad, Ross! I don't think
I've ever been this angry!
돌아버리겠네, 이렇게
열이 올라보긴 처음이야
What about when I said
we were on a break?
내가 '그땐 헤어졌었어'라고
말할 때는?
-Nice car.
-Yeah, it's not mine.
차 멋지군요
제 차 아닌데요
-I love your car.
-Yeah, it's mine.
근사한 차네요
네... 제 차예요
-I bet it's fast.
-Me too. Yeah.
- 상당히 빠르죠?
- 빠를 겁니다
And comfortable.
그리고 편안하죠
- 가죽시트 좋아하세요?
- 네
-You like leather seats?
-Yeah.
It's got them!
가죽이랍니다
Phoebe, how's it going?
피비, 어때?
이 정도면 할 만하다
애들이 좋아하는 것 같니?
I'm okay. Are they having fun?
Am I talking too fast?
- 내 말이 너무 빨라?
- 아니, 나 정도인데 뭐
No. You sound like me.
It's going great. Look at Chandler
with Little Baby Girl Chandler.
잘하고 있어
챈들러가 꼬마숙녀 챈들러를
안고 있는 것 좀 봐
Little Baby Girl Chandler. Where have
I heard that before? Oh, Coach Rubin.
꼬마숙녀 챈들러라
어디서 많이 들어봤는데
맞다, 루벤 코치였어
Phoebe, when you're done over there,
we've got a situation over here too.
피비, 그쪽 일 끝나면
이쪽 상황도 정리해 줘
No. We are all responsible
for our own babies.
안 돼, 자기 아기는
자기가 돌봐야지
그게 아니지
That's where you're wrong.
We've been playing them man-to-man.
대인방어가 아니라
지역방어를 해야 돼
We should really be playing
a zone defense.
What do you mean?
무슨 말이야?
각자 역할을 분담하면
훨씬 수월하다는 거지
Things'll go smoother if we each have a
zone. Phoebe, be in charge of wiping.
피비는 닦아주는 역할
모니카는 기저귀 교환
Mon, be in charge of diapering.
I'll be in charge of looking at how cute
they are when they put their hands...
난 얘들이 잼잼 할 때
쓰다듬어 주는 사람
Sounds great, but you should be
in charge of wiping.
좋은 생각인데 네가
닦아주는 사람 해라
난 신인이라 공격하면 안 돼
Okay, I'm a rookie.
I should not be in the end zone.
This is so great. This is exactly how
we set the plates at the restaurant.
멋지다, 식당에서 접시
놓을 때 이렇게 하는데
Yeah? Well, this is not
what I ordered.
이건 내가 주문한 게 아냐
Hey, guys.
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
Hey, babies.
안녕, 아그들아
정말 신나는 아침이었어
I'm having the best morning.
내가 키 갖고 있는 포르쉐
아직 거기 있어
That Porsche I've got the keys to?
Still there.
쇼킹이다
아직 키를 갖고 있다니
Shocking, since you
still have the keys.
You should see the treatment I get
with that car.
그 차 옆에 서있을 때
사람들 반응이 어떤지 알아?
People are friendly. They wanna talk.
And not just about the car.
친한 척하면서 말을 붙이고
차 얘기만이 아니라
One guy advised me
on my equity investments.
주식투자에 대해
충고한 사람도 있었어
What equity investments?
웬 주식투자?
주식해서 포르쉐 샀잖아
관심 좀 가져라
The ones that got me the Porsche.
Will you keep up?
If people see me just standing there,
they're gonna think I don't own it.
그냥 서있으면 내가 주인이
아니라고 생각할 거야
So I figure I'll wash it.
Monica, you got a bucket and soap?
그래서 세차를 하기로 했어
모니카, 양동이랑
세제 좀 빌려줄래?
그래, 세제에다 스펀지
걸레, 왁스, 광택제도 있어
Oh, yeah. I got soap
and sponges and rags...
and carnauba wax
and polishing compound.
You don't even have a car.
넌 차도 없잖아
I know. Once there was a dirty car in
front of the building, so I washed it.
근데 언젠가 건물 앞에
너무 더러운 차가 있어서
내가 세차를 했거든
-And?
-And six others.
그리고?
- 여섯 대 더 했어
- 그럼 그렇지
There you are.
Yeah, she tops out at 130.
네, 130은 나옵니다
That's just in the city.
I get her up to 160 upstate.
시내에 있을 때 얘기죠
북쪽에선 보통 160 놔요
Really? You got a place upstate?
정말요?
북쪽에 사세요?
Sure.
그럼요
-All right. See you later.
-Okay. Take it easy.
- 그래요, 또 봅시다
- 네, 잘 가요
Hey. That's my car.
이봐요
이건 내 차예요
Really?
그래요?
Just give me five more minutes.
5분만 있어봐요
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거죠?
I found the keys and now
I'm just polishing her up.
키를 주웠거든요
광 좀 내는 중이죠
-But it's my car.
-Yeah, but it's my wax.
내 차라니까요
그래도 왁스는 내 겁니다
Listen, I don't come to the city much.
이 동네는 자주
안 와서 모르겠는데
당신이 미친 거요
아님 무슨 거리공연인가요?
I don't know if you're crazy or
if this is some street theater...
but could I have my keys?
어쨌든 키나 주실래요?
Sure. Yeah.
I'll save your parking spot.
네, 그럽시다
- 주차공간은 맡아놓죠
- 이제 안 옵니다
I'm not coming back.
-Why not?
-I live upstate.
왜요?
북쪽에 살거든요
Yeah, so did I.
네, 나도 그래요
I don't know why I was so nervous...
괜히 지레 겁을 먹었나봐
and why Frank and Alice complain.
This is easy.
별것도 아닌데 동생 부부는
왜 늘 푸념을 늘어놓지?
Yeah, two hours, a lifetime,
that's the same.
두 시간 만에 박사 되셨네
Check it out!
When the babies wake up...
자, 기대하시라
애들 일어나면
크록이랑 놀 거야
they can meet Krog!
That thing could put
someone's eye out.
그게 뭐야, 눈이라도
다치면 어떡하려고
He can do more than that.
He can destroy the universe.
얘는 눈 정도가 아니라
우주를 파괴할 수 있어
안 돼, 물어뜯어서
삼키면 큰일이잖아
They could swallow
one of those little parts.
Also, look at his smooth area.
That's just gonna mess them up.
사실 그 매끈한 데가
더 위험하지만
1살짜리한테 맞는
장난감이 아냐
It's just not an appropriate toy
for 1-year-olds. Or 30-year-olds.
30살짜리한테도
They won't swallow anything.
You're too overprotective.
삼키기는 뭘 삼키나
이건 과보호야
When I was a kid, my mom used to throw
me into a pile of broken glass.
우리 엄마는 옛날에 깨진
유리더미에 날 던지곤 했어
-What?
-Glass, sand, whatever.
뭐?
유리나 모래나 그게 그거지
Look at little Leslie stretching
in her sleep.
레슬리가 자면서 운동하네
Oh, it's so cute.
너무 귀여워
I wonder when you stop putting
both legs behind your head.
어른이 되면 양쪽 다리가
머리 뒤로 안 올라가지?
I can still do that.
난 아직도 돼
How are you still single?
너 어떻게 아직도 싱글이니?
I thought about it and maybe you're
right. Maybe Krog is not a safe toy.
생각해봤는데 너희 말대로
안전한 장난감이 아닌가봐
-What made you change your mind?
-I swallowed his sonic blaster gun.
왜 마음을 바꿨어?
초음파 우주총을 삼켰거든
How did that happen?
어쩌다 그랬어?
I was trying to prove
that I was right.
내 말이 맞다는 걸
증명하려고 했는데
And it turns out I was wrong...
알고 보니 틀렸더라고
and now it's lodged in my throat.
목에 딱 걸렸지 뭐야
This whole time we were
concentrating on the babies...
아기들한테만 정신이 팔려서
챈들러를 돌보지 않았구나
and no one was watching Chandler!
You are asking the court
for an annulment?
혼인무효신청을 하셨죠?
네, 재판장님
서류를 작성해 왔습니다
Yes, Your Honor. Here are
our forms, all filled out.
So based on your petition...
소장에 의하면
무효신청의 이유가...
you are seeking an annulment
on the grounds...
that "Mr. Geller
is mentally unstable."
겔러 씨의 정서불안
때문이군요
Fine. I'm mentally unstable.
네, 정서불안입니다
And based on the fact that "Mr. Geller
is an intravenous drug user."
그리고 겔러 씨의
마약주사 상용
-What?
-Yes. Heroin and crack.
뭐요?
네, 헤로인과 코카인
Crack isn't even an intravenous drug.
코카인은 주사로 하는
마약이 아냐
Well, you would know.
역시 잘 아시네
또 혼인 전에 자신의
성적취향을 속였군요
Now, it also says here that you...
"lied about your sexual preference
before marriage."
- 이거 왜 이래
- 로스, 그 잡지 다 봤어
Oh, come on.
Ross, please. I found the magazines.
And finally, that you were
"unable to consummate the marriage."
마지막으로 성생활을
유지할 능력이 없다
Well, that makes sense since
you're gay and addicted to heroin.
헤로인에 중독된 게이라면
당연한 결과겠죠
You know, I'm sorry, this is insane.
죄송하지만
이건 말도 안 됩니다
전 헤로인 중독도 아니고
게이도 아니고
I'm not addicted to heroin,
I'm not gay and there is no problem...
성생활 유지에도
전혀 문제없습니다
with my ability
to consummate anything.
당장 이 자리에서
증명할 수 있어요
I'll consummate this marriage
right here, right now!
That won't be necessary.
그럴 필요는 없습니다
한참 사귈 때는
토끼처럼 해댔죠
And when we were dating,
we consummated like bunnies.
If you were involved in a serious
relationship, that creates a problem.
두 분이 심각하게
사귄 적이 있다면 문제가...
말씀드리지만 그 관계는
2년 전에 끝났답니다
Rest assured, that relationship
ended two years ago.
그리고 토끼 얘기는
기록에서 삭제해주세요
Strike "consummated like bunnies"
from the record.
Is there anything in this record
that is actually true?
여기 적힌 내용 중에
사실이 하나라도 있나요?
Well, yes. We got married in Vegas.
네, 라스베가스에서
결혼한 거랑...
And the names, I think.
이름 정도네요
이렇게는 법적용이 되지 않아요
That's not the way
the legal system works.
This process is based on an objective
review of the facts, not of the lies.
거짓말이 아니라 객관적인
사실에 근거해야 합니다
이의 있습니다
Objection!
- 그렇게도 안 됩니다
- 기각합니다
-It doesn't work like that either.
-Overruled.
그만해
Oh, stop it.
Based on what I've heard, you certainly
don't qualify for an annulment.
지금 들은 얘기로는 두 분의
혼인을 취소할 수 없겠군요
If you don't wanna be together,
file for divorce.
함께 살 수 없다면
이혼소송을 하세요
That's great. You happy? Look what
you did with your funny, funny form.
잘됐다, 이제 행복하냐?
구비서류 아주 잘 만들었다
What? Me? What about you and your
"consummated like bunnies" nonsense?
남 얘기하지 마
넌 어떻고
토끼 얘기나 한 주제에
뭐...
What are you typing that for?
She said we don't get the annulment.
지금 뭘 치는 거요?
못 들었어요?
기각됐잖아요
Don't type that. What..
치지 말라니까
Stop typing!
그만 칩시다
이봐요!
Stop typing!
그만 치쇼
"Stop typing, stop typing!"
'그만 치쇼'라고 그만 치쇼!
자, 한번 보세요
이런 사람이랑 살라고요?
Okay, do you see what you're
keeping me married to?
Get out of my chambers.
그만 나가주세요
아줌마, 똑똑히 들어요
Lady, here's the deal.
I came here for an annulment and
I'm not leaving here until I get one!
혼인이 취소되기 전엔
한 발자국도 못 움직여요
하룻밤 철창신세 지고 싶나요?
-Would you like a night in jail?
-Thank you for your time.
시간 내주셔서 감사합니다
주인이 포르쉐 찾아갔다
That Porsche guy took his car back.
But you found the keys to his clothes?
대신 그 사람
옷장 열쇠를 주웠냐?
No, I just love the way it feels
when everybody thinks I own a Porsche.
그게 아니라...
포르쉐 주인이 된 기분이
그렇게 나쁘진 않더라고
They'll think you own one
because of the clothes?
그 옷을 입으면
포르쉐 주인처럼 보여?
Of course.
당연한 말씀
Only an idiot would wear this stuff
if he didn't have the car.
포르쉐도 없는데
이런 걸 입으면 푼수지
That is true.
그건 진실이다
Yeah, but only a genius would
swallow a sonic blaster gun.
맞아, 천재나 되니까
초음파 우주총을 삼키지
Oh, I've been there.
그 기분 내 알지
I am gonna go drive my Porsche.
난 포르쉐나 몰아야겠다
You know you don't actually have one.
조이, 넌 그런 차 없잖아
제발 산통 좀 깨지 마라
누가 쟤 좀 말려 줘
What are you doing? I'm in character.
Will you talk to her?
I think it just moved.
It's poking me.
약간 움직였어
콕콕 찌르는데?
아무래도 병원에 가야겠다
We'll go to the emergency room.
No, you can't leave me here with them.
We're babysitting.
뭐야? 나만 두고 간다고?
우리 애 보는 중이잖아
The babies are asleep.
You'll be okay on your own.
다들 자고 있잖아
잠깐이니까 괜찮을 거야
그래도 가면 안 돼
You can't leave me with them.
We're a team.
우린 팀이야, 지역방어인데
3대 1로 붙으라는 거야?
We're playing a zone.
They'll triple-team me!
He's got plastic in his throat.
We gotta go to the hospital.
목에 플라스틱이 걸렸어
병원에 가야 돼
But a doctor won't be able to help him.
And it's just gonna...
의사라고 별수 있겠어?
그냥 두면 내려올 거야
한 7년쯤 뒤에
naturally pass through
his system in seven years.
-I think that's gum.
-I'm pretty sure it's gun.
그건 껌 아냐?
틀림없이 총이야
This really hurts. Let's go.
진짜 아파, 가자
But no! A real man wouldn't
just run to the hospital.
사나이라면 병원에
쪼르르 안 달려간다
크록도 그랬을까?
No! What would Krog do?
Why isn't that valet back
with my Porsche?
이 친구 왜 내 포르쉐를
안 갖고 오는 걸까?
Maybe because you've got the keys?
키가 댁한테 있구만 뭐
포르쉐
-That was totally your fault.
-My fault? You threatened the judge.
다 네 잘못이야
내 잘못? 판사를
협박한 건 너야
You ripped the paper out
of the court reporter's machine!
속기사 타자용지를
찢어버린 건 누군데
안 그랬으면
계속 칠 기세였다고!
That was the only way I could
get him to stop typing!
반갑소이다, 겔러 부부
Hi. How are the Gellers?
Don't call us that.
우릴 그렇게 부르지 마
The judge wouldn't let us get an
annulment. Now we gotta get a divorce!
무효신청이 기각됐어
이제 남은 건 이혼이지
Did a Porsche throw up on you?
포르쉐가 너한테 토하고 갔냐?
임마! 포르쉐 욕하지 마!
It's "Porsche-a"!
Me taking care of you
is no problem, huh?
고모도 이렇게 잘해
너희도 좋지? 안 그래?
You guys feel safe, right?
I'm gonna take that spit bubble
as a "Yeah, I do!"
그 침방울은
'네, 맞아요'란 뜻이지?
더러운 기저귀는 버리고
깨끗한 걸로 채워야겠다
Let's get rid of this dirty diaper.
I'll set you up with a clean one.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
I just have to clean that up.
저런, 미안
놀랐다면 미안해
일단 치우자
Because, let's face it,
we're at Monica's.
여긴 모니카 집이니까
I broke it. All right.
Well, that's just the way things go.
깨졌네, 그래
어쩔 수 없지 뭐
Okay. Good.
됐다, 좋았어
Why are there only two of you?
왜 너희 둘만 있니?
Where's Leslie?
레슬리 어쨌어?
Well, you can't answer.
Leslie? Where are you, Leslie?
너흰 대답 못하지, 레슬리?
어디 있니, 레슬리?
Now would be a good time
for your first words.
이번 기회에 말문을 열어보렴
거기 있었구나
Well, look at you!
You are a little bit mischievous.
My gosh!
이런 말썽꾸러기 같으니
세상에
Oh, you're a lot mischievous.
말썽이 좀 심했구나
Well, it'll dry.
뭐, 마르겠지
이제 동생들한테 가자
You sit with your brother
and sister now...
who aren't there.
얘들은 또 왜 없어
갔다왔어
How do you feel?
좀 어때?
Let's just say Krog will be equipped
to destroy the universe again...
반나절 정도 지나면 크록이
다시 완전무장을 할 수 있어
in 12 to 14 hours.
다행이다, 아기들을
내가 혼자 다 돌봤어
I totally took care of the babies
all by myself.
먹이고 씻기고 재웠지
I fed them, bathed them
and put them to bed.
And protected them from a tornado?
토네이도까지 막아줬냐?
Oh, my God!
엄마야
I know. The babies are asleep.
알아, 애들 다 잔다
Phoebe, what happened here?
이게 대체 무슨 난리야
I did it. I took care
of the babies all by myself.
내가 해냈어
혼자서 애들을 돌봤어
-But my apartment!
-Was the setting of Phoebe's triumph.
- 내 아파트는?
- 피비가 대승한 전장이지
난장판이야
But the mess!
피비가 혼자서 아기들을
돌봤다는 게 더 중요하지
Is not as important as the fact
that Phoebe took care of the babies.
You're right. I shouldn't freak out.
맞아
화내면 안 되지
This is what it'll be like
when we have babies. When's that?
우리도 아이 가지면 이렇게
될 테니까, 그게 언제일까?
Phoebe, look at this mess!
피비, 집안 꼴이 이게 뭐야!
Oh, honey. Thank God you're home.
I was getting worried.
여보, 이제 왔군요
많이 걱정했는데
I picked up the divorce papers.
이혼서류를 가져왔어
I've already signed everything.
I put little X's where you need to sign.
난 서명까지 끝냈고
X표 쳐둔 곳에
네가 서명하면 돼
어머, 조그만 X표네
이거면 다 용서되지
Little X's. Great!
That makes up for everything.
You know, you've done
a lot of stupid stuff too, okay?
모르나 본데 너도
바보 같은 짓 많이 했어
이거보다 더 바보 같은 짓
있으면 하나만 대봐
Name one stupid thing that is
as stupid as this one.
내 결혼식 막으려고
런던으로 날아온 건?
How about you flew to London
to stop my wedding?
결혼한 다음에
날 사랑한다고 말한 건?
You told me you loved me
after I was married.
잠깐, 그건 다른 얘기야
그땐 사랑했으니까 그런 거지
Wait, that was different. I did those
things because I was in love with you.
그래, 맞아
Right.
You're right. That's very different.
맞는 말이다
그건 다른 얘기지
So let's just sign the papers.
됐으니까 서명이나 해라
What?
왜?
Nothing.
아냐
Okay, can we just sign, please?
좋아, 여기다 하면 돼
Congratulations.
축하한다
Okay, wait, Ross. Wait a minute.
저기, 로스
잠깐만
- 사실은 고백할 게 있어
- 뭔데?
I kind of have a little confession.
What?
이 결혼식 사건 있잖아
Well, you know,
this whole marriage thing.
Kind of my idea.
실은 내 생각이었어
Excuse me?
뭐라고?
결혼하던 날 밤 너무 취해서
아무 것도 기억이 안 났잖아
Remember how we were too drunk to
remember anything when we were married?
그래
정말 이 얘기는
하기 싫었는데
I didn't really wanna say anything,
but it just kept coming back to me.
조금씩 기억이 나더라고
카지노에서 그랬잖아, 포도를
많이 먹으면 재미있을 거라고
We were in the casino and you thought
it'd be funny to eat a lot of grapes.
And I thought it would be funnier
if we got married.
난 결혼하는 게
더 재미있겠더라고
So as a compromise we decided
first to get married and then...
서로 절충을 해서
먼저 결혼부터 하고...
to eat a lot of grapes.
포도를 먹기로 했거든
어쨌든 이런 소동을
일으켜서 미안해
Sorry I got us into this whole thing.
So then if you think about it...
그런 식으로 생각하면
이게 몽땅...
this is all your fault.
네 잘못이네
너무 강조하진 마
Yeah, don't push it, though.
I gotta say...
사실 난...
I know I divorce a lot of women.
많은 여자랑 이혼했지만
Never thought I'd be divorcing you.
너랑 이혼할 거라곤
전혀 생각 못했어
I know.
알아
I always thought if we got married,
that'd be the one that stuck.
만약 우리가 결혼하면 쉽게
깨지진 않을 거라 생각했어
And it wouldn't be a secret...
비밀로 할 필요도 없고
and we wouldn't have our
wedding dinner at Pizza Hut.
피자헛에서 피로연을
하지도 않았을 거야
Did I even treat?
내가 돈을 내긴 했던가?
아니, 신혼 스페셜이라
공짜로 먹었지
No, it was on the house.
It was a newlywed special.
That may be the most depressing thing
I've heard.
내 생애 최고로
우울한 스토리다
그래
I should get these
to my lawyer's office.
이거 변호사한테 갖다줘야겠다
그래, 잘 처리해줘서 고마워
Thanks for taking care of all this.
뭘, 괜찮아
No problem.
-I'm gonna need a copy of those.
-Totally.
- 그거 복사해 줘
- 당연하지
이 친구야, 조심해
내 포르쉐 다치잖아
Careful around my Porsche!
Hi, Joey.
반가워요, 조이
저런, 안녕하쇼
Hey. How you doing?
He has the most amazing Porsche
under there.
이 사람 포르쉐
정말 끝내주거든
I'd show you, but I just tucked
her in. She's sleeping.
저도 보여드리고 싶지만
방금 잠자리에 들었거든요
술이나 한잔하러 갈까요?
Would you like to go for a drink?